http://www.clevelandjewishnews.com/site/privacy.html

Beachwood, OH
(44122)
Today
Partly cloudy skies in the morning will give way to cloudy skies during the afternoon. High 52F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Cloudy. Low 44F. Winds SSE at 5 to 10 mph.
Top Story
In-person lighting, virtual event highlight first night of Chanukah in Solon
On the first night of Chanukah, Jews in Solon pivoted using a hybrid format to allow viewers at home on Zoom to view the lighting taking place in the parking lot of Solon Chabad in Solon.
More Headlines
US panel endorses widespread use of Pfizer COVID-19 vaccine
Fudge to speak at Fairmount Temple’s MLK Shabbat service Jan. 15
Park Synagogue wants you to shout ‘bingo’ to aid Family Promise
Virtual classes, services and offerings, starting December 11
Features
Business
Camps
CJN TV
Education
Health
Holidays
Nosh
Religious Life
Silver Linings
Special Sections
UNFILTERED
Top Story
The Temple-Tifereth Israel seeks to light 1,000 hanukkiah
The Temple-Tifereth Israel in Beachwood will attempt to set a record for the most hanukkiah lit virtually Dec. 11.
More Headlines
Having will, estate can make situation easier for family
Senior communities adjust for Festival of Lights
Synagogue service times: Week of December 11
The easiest Chanukah jelly doughnut recipe ever
Opinion
CJN Columnists
Guest Columns
Letters to the Editor
Op-Eds
CJN Accidental Blogger
Polls
Top Story
Columbus getting kick out of Crew’s Cup appearance
Last weekend, Jimmy Haslam received good news about two of his teams.
More Headlines
Test results can be misleading
Netanyahu maneuvering may lead to fourth election
Estate plan – business decision or value statement
Some healthy resolutions for 2021
Community
Lifecycles
In the Community
The City
18 Difference Makers
My Israel
Circle of Life
Top Story
Latnik, Michael
On Dec. 3, 2020, Michael R. Latnik suddenly and unexpectedly passed away at age 61. He was the beloved husband of Tina (nee Salvia) Latnik; devoted son of Donald and Roberta (nee Gluchov) Latnik; dear brother of Jackie Crossland (nee Latnik) and Toby (Robert Lawson) Latnik; loving uncle of R…
More Headlines
Obituaries
Tolin, Bernard
Obituaries
Teitel, Jeffrey
Obituaries
Ettkin, Eileen
Obituaries
Home
Your privacy is important to us at The Cleveland Jewish News (“CJN.org”). Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use carefully. By visiting this website you are agreeing to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.The Types of Information We CollectWe gather information from you in three ways:1) Information Gathered by Voluntary SubmissionYou are not required to provide information about yourself when visiting CJN.org. However, to make use of certain features on our website, such as requesting subscriptions or e-newsletters, entering contests, sending letters to the editor, accessing interactive forums and submitting information for lifecycle events, visitors need to provide personal information as part of the process. We may ask, for example, for:Contact information, including, name, address, email address, phone number, facsimile number, and mobile number;User name, password, and password reminder questions and answers;Age and date of birth;Other demographic information, such as gender, job information, and postal code;Public information, including profile information, you provide CJN.org for the publication, such as your user name, comments, likes, interests, status, pictures and the address of your website;Communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive;Search queries;If you are ordering a subscription, we will ask for a credit card number and date of expiration.In limited circumstances, payment and identification verification information, such as a credit card number, social security number or comparable national identifiers, and driver’s license number where needed for payment, to complete a particular transaction, or to access a particular service (e.g. contests);Information posted in community discussion and other interactive online features;Correspondence you sent to us; andInformation collected about you offline (including via facsimile, postal mail, or in person and CJN.org sponsored events or contest entrance forms).The information you supply will help us satisfy your requests and allow us to offer more personalized features and make our site more useful to you. Supplying information is entirely voluntary. Please note that if you do not supply the information we request, you will not be able to access that service.2) Information Automatically Gathered About All VisitorsCJN.org may collect other certain types of information about you automatically, including,Your browser type and operating system;Your Internet Protocol (IP) address;Websites you visited before and after visiting CJN.org;Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on within CJN.org;Unique identifiers, including mobile device information numbers, that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law;Information collected through cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies;Information about your Interactions with audio and video content, such as the type of content listened to (including music applications like iTunes, Spotify and Last.fm) and content viewed, and about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded;Standard server log information;3) Information We Obtain From Other SourcesWhen permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (e.g. mobile devices, third party services, and embedded audio and video players), co-branded partners and websites (for example our Facebook page), and from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources:Name, postal address, and telephone number;Demographic data, such as age, gender, and income level;If you access third party services (e.g. Facebook, Google+ ,Twitter, or Yahoo) through a CJN.org service, your username and password for those services and other information available about you on those services, as described in our Social Networking Policy below;Your interests and purchase behavior;Publicly-observed data, such as activity on blogs, videos, and other online postings; andOther navigation data, such as websites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on.The Privacy Policy does cover the practices of third parties, including our advertisers, partners, and other content providers and those that may disclose information to CJN.org. Please also note that all of the information we collect about you may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across CJN.org.The Way We Use Information We CollectWe generally use information we collect about you to:Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to send you electronic newsletters, authorize a purchase, and complete a transaction that you have requested;Enable you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes and message boards;Provide you with special offers and promotional materials on behalf of CJN.org, companies within our corporate family, and third parties, in accordance with applicable law;Analyze the use of CJN.org by visitors to our website and use of our services to understand and improve our offerings and, in accordance with below to produce anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop their own products and service offerings;Customize the content you see when you visit CJN.org;Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests;Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and otherwise in accordance with the CJN.org Terms of Use; andFor any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.We present the information we automatically gather about all visitors to our advertisers, in order to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website. We provide the information to the advertisers in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our website.We may also share the personal data you provide to us by voluntary submission with parties that market products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. This personal information may include your email address or other information such as your name, address, age, phone number or sex. While we will seek to require such third parties to follow the provisions of our privacy policy and will not authorize them to use your personal data except for the purpose for which it was provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of any third parties.We only use the credit card number and date of expiration you provide when placing an order for a subscription only to complete that order. We only use other similar information we may collect such as drivers license number, social security numbers, or comparable national identifiers as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a server (paid subscriptions or awarding a prize to contest winners) or as otherwise required by law. We do not share that information with any outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Although CJN.org may provide links to other sites and other sites may provide links to CJN.org, we do not control the data collection practices of those other sites or the privacy policy and practices of those sites.The Cleveland Jewish News may use remarketing features available through the Google display network. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. These vendors use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to our website.Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Disclosure of InformationCJN.org may disclose your information collected about you as follows:Authorized Third Party Service ProvidersWe share your contact information with third party vendors who help us with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, suppression list management, and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your contact information to help us provide our services and not for any other purpose. Also, authorized third party service providers may collect non-contact information about your visits to our services with cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies that may be used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests.Sweepstakes, Contests, or PromotionsWhen you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, and in accordance with the terms and conditions of the promotions, your information may be disclosed to our sponsors and to third parties who help administer the promotion, including in connection with winner selection prize fulfillment and aggregated data analysis. Your information also may be disclosed as required by law, such as on a winners list. Further, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, including allowing our sponsors to use your name, voice, and likeness in advertising and marketing associated with the promotion in accordance with applicable law. All terms applicable to the particular promotion will be made available to you at the time you enter the promotion.Co-Branded PartnersCo-Branded Partners are third parties with whom CJN.org may offer jointly a service or feature. You will be able to tell when you are accessing a service or feature offered by a Co-Branded Partner, because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. By doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may also apply to its use of your information.CJN.org And Other Cleveland Jewish Publication Co.CJN.org and other business units of Cleveland Jewish Publication Co. continue to expand their online presence in order to offer users rich and deep interactive experiences. Where permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you within any parent, subsidiary, or other affiliate of CJN.org and the Cleveland Jewish Publication Co., so that we can provide you with information about products and services that might interest you.Business TransfersAlthough highly unlikely given our purpose and structure, we may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a CJN.org a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the event of bankruptcy.Legal RequirementsWe may disclose information about our users, including contact information, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures, and to comply with other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements.Protect CJN.org Services And UsersWe may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of CJN.org, Cleveland Jewish Publication Co., or other Cleveland Jewish Publication Co. affiliated companies, and their employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements); to protect the safety and security of users of our website, services, and members of the public; and as otherwise disclosed in the CJN.org’s Terms of Use.Please note that we may share information with advertisers as described above.In addition, information collected about your interactions with audio and video content may be shared with third parties, including third party social networking services such as Facebook, and video measurement and subscription services such as Reuters or Nielsen.Finally, we also may share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties to help us develop content and services we hope will interest you or to help these third parties develop their own product and service offerings, including targeted marketing, as described in our overview of third party online advertising.Comments and User Generated ContentWe offer readers a chance to comment on articles on CJN.org. Publication of user-generated content on CJN.org is subject to our Terms of Use. These public activities are visible to other visitors to the site. Information you disclose or provide in a comment, including your login name or Facebook profile, are made public. The Cleveland Jewish News takes no responsibility for any information you submit publically on our website and any information you do choose to publish is at your own risk. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety. You should also be aware that we may also engage a third party to provide some of the services associated with the blogs, message boards, comments, and similar functions. This third party will collect and host the information that you submit to CJN.org, but will not use any of this information for purposes other than providing the service. User generated comments on our website and/or social media pages, or other publications may be deleted or removed at the discretion of the Cleveland Jewish News at any time and without notice to the user.Social Networking ServicesCJN.org has partnered with certain third party social networking companies to offer you their services through CJN.org. For example, you can use third party social networking services such as Facebook, Yahoo, Google+ or Twitter to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activities on a CJN.org, and they also may notify your friends, both on CJN.org and on their services, that you are CJN.org user or about your use of the CJN.org services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies.By using your CJN.org account with a third party social networking service, you consent to share information about you, including video content that you have watched on CJN.org, with your friends and followers on those services. You can limit how third party social networking services share your information by visiting your social networking services’ websites and updating your privacy settings.In addition, CJN.org may request your permission to a) access and collect information available from your social networking account; and b) post information to your friends on your behalf. When you connect your social networking service with your CJN.org account, you authorize CJN.org to access certain information about you from your social networking service to provide content and services, including helping us tailor our communications to you and develop rich online content and services across the CJN.org. The information CJN.org may access from your social networking services is governed by the privacy policies and settings of those third party services.Third Party Websites And ServicesPlease note that some CJN.org services or webpages may contain links to other websites and services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each website that you visit. When you select a link to a third party website from CJN.org, you will be leaving the CJN.org website. Any information that you disclose on the third party website will be governed by that website's privacy policy.California VisitorsResidents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which CJN.org has disclosed certain information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like such a list, please contact us at webinfo@cjn.org. If you are a California resident under 18 years of age, and a registered user of any website where this policy is posted, you may request removal of content or information you have publicly posted. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you posted and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal, even if requested.For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your request and include the name of the CJN.org webpage and/or service with respect to which you are requesting the information. You must also include your full name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We will not accept requests via telephone, postal mail, or facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.Transfer of Data InternationallyCJN.org is headquartered in the United States, but may, from time to time have affiliates and partners in other countries. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of CJN.org may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in the country to which your information is transferred may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using and participating in any CJN.org service or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information.Security of InformationTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration for the information we collect online. Viewing and Correcting Your InformationIf at any time you would like to (a) verify the accuracy of the information you have provided to us, or (b) correct that information, please contact us in writing at webinfo@cjn.org. We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to disclosing any personal information or making any of the requested changes to personal information.Opting OutIf you prefer that we not share any of the information you have provided to us with third parties, you may "opt out" by contacting webinfo@cjn.org.Email PolicyThe Cleveland Jewish News complies with the federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. Therefore if you opt out of receiving certain emails from us, we will not send you those emails. You can opt-out of receiving emails from us by following the “unsubscribe” instructions at the bottom of each email we send you.We offer several types of emails, including our daily Boker Tov daily email, Liecycles and as-it-happens breaking news. If you no longer wish to remain on a particular email list, you can change your preferences at the bottom of each email.If you have provided us with your email address, we may use it to survey you to collect feedback about your experiences with our products. This helps us improve our services to better serve you.If you feel you have received an email from us in error, please contact webinfo@cjn.org.Guidelines for CHILDRENProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We comply with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Children must get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as name, email address and telephone number) over the Internet, to us or anyone else. We encourage parents to review and share safety concerns and tips with their children participating in online activity.We do not specifically collect or maintain information from children. If we receive actual knowledge that a user of our website is under the age of 13 and has provided personal information to us we will immediately remove all such information from our database. In order to transmit certain information to our website (b'nai mitzvah, birth announcements, etc.), however, adults are asked to provide information about children (name, birth date, age). Although we will collect this information through our website about children, it will not be shared with partners or other third parties.Amendments To Privacy PolicyThe Web is an evolving medium. Accordingly, we reserve the right to amend the terms of our privacy policy at any time.If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. Of course, our use of information gathered while a certain policy is in effect will always be consistent with that certain policy, even if we change that policy later. If we decide to use your information for a purpose other than that stated in our policy at the time we collected your information, we will notify you and give you a choice as to whether you would allow us to use the information for that different purpose. By making changes to your personal information after our privacy policy has been amended, you consent to the terms of our policy as amended.This privacy policy was last amended on January 12, 2016. If you have any questions about privacy or your use of cjn.org, please contact us at webinfo@cjn.org.
Sign up for e-newsChoose from the CJN's informative e-newsletters.
Sign up
Latest E-edition
Read the latest edition of the Cleveland Jewish News anytime on your desktop, tablet or mobile device. E-edition subscribers have access to the CJN a day earlier than print subscribers and have unlimited access to our digital archives.
Submit your events
Upcoming events
Dec
11
A Festival of Lights
Fri, Dec 11, 2020
Free
Dec
Crohn's and Colitis Foundation of America Concord support group meeting
Between the Screens: A Conversation with Steven Caple Jr.
Thu, Dec 17, 2020
$20
More briefs
Briefs
Fudge to speak at Fairmount Temple’s MLK Shabbat service Jan. 15
Health care workers share struggles on the front lines as COVID-19 cases surge
+3
Local News
Kosher Food Pantry uses heated trailers, shifts to meet needs
© Copyright 2020 Cleveland Jewish News, 23880 Commerce Park, Suite 1 Beachwood, OH  | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
